http://www.jensenit.com/about-us/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Des Plaines, IL | JensenIT
Your
IT Support Experts
We partner with many types of businesses, and strive to eliminate IT issues before they cause expensive downtime.
Login
Register
HomeLogin / LogoutCreate an AccountStoresAbout UsWho We AreOur DifferenceIT Industry SecretTestimonialsEmploymentRefer a Colleague or FriendPrivacy PolicyReturn PolicyIT ServicesBusiness CommunicationConferencingConferencing and CollaborationMobile Device ManagementUnified CommunicationsVoIPCloud Computing ServicesCloud Backup & File SharingCloud Hosted VoIPCloud IT SolutionsHardware VirtualizationHosted Microsoft ExchangeMicrosoft AzureData ServicesBusiness ContinuityCabling and WiringDisaster Recovery as a ServiceHardware ServicesComputer RepairHardware as a ServiceHigh-Speed Internet ConsultingHP Official DealerLenovo Official ResellerOffice Relocation ServicesOfficial Dell DealerPrinter ManagementServer MigrationWireless ServicesIndustry SpecificAccountingEducationElectronic Medical RecordsEngineers and ArchitectsHealthcareLaw PracticesManufacturingRetailSupply Chain and LogisticsIT Security ServicesAccess Control SolutionsContent FilteringEmail EncryptionEnterprise Mobility Management SolutionsNetwork SecuritySecurity CamerasSecurity NetworkingSOPHOS Security SolutionsSpam ProtectionWatchGuard Unified Threat ManagementManaged IT Services24/7 Help DeskBusiness Computing AssessmentCo-Managed ITComprehensive IT SupportDesktop Monitoring and ManagementInfrastructure Support ServicesIT ConsultingIT Vendor ManagementManaged ServicesMicrosoft Hyper-VProfessional Server SupportRemote Monitoring & MaintenanceVMwareSoftware ServicesMicrosoft Office 365Microsoft Partner NetworkUnderstanding ITAutomationBusiness ContinuityBYODCloud ComputingGDPR ComplianceHIPAAIT Threat GlossaryNetwork SecurityPCI DSSRansomwareSOXThe Internet of ThingsThe Modern OfficeWindows 10NewsNews & Press ReleasesEvents CalendarOur NewsletterBlogContact UsSupportHow to Request SupportHelp Desk
Free
Consultation
Interested in seeing what we can do for your business? Contact us to see how we can help you! Sign Up Today
(847) 803-0044LoginRegister
HomeLogin / LogoutCreate an AccountStoresAbout UsWho We AreOur DifferenceIT Industry SecretTestimonialsEmploymentRefer a Colleague or FriendPrivacy PolicyReturn PolicyIT ServicesBusiness CommunicationConferencingConferencing and CollaborationMobile Device ManagementUnified CommunicationsVoIPCloud Computing ServicesCloud Backup & File SharingCloud Hosted VoIPCloud IT SolutionsHardware VirtualizationHosted Microsoft ExchangeMicrosoft AzureData ServicesBusiness ContinuityCabling and WiringDisaster Recovery as a ServiceHardware ServicesComputer RepairHardware as a ServiceHigh-Speed Internet ConsultingHP Official DealerLenovo Official ResellerOffice Relocation ServicesOfficial Dell DealerPrinter ManagementServer MigrationWireless ServicesIndustry SpecificAccountingEducationElectronic Medical RecordsEngineers and ArchitectsHealthcareLaw PracticesManufacturingRetailSupply Chain and LogisticsIT Security ServicesAccess Control SolutionsContent FilteringEmail EncryptionEnterprise Mobility Management SolutionsNetwork SecuritySecurity CamerasSecurity NetworkingSOPHOS Security SolutionsSpam ProtectionWatchGuard Unified Threat ManagementManaged IT Services24/7 Help DeskBusiness Computing AssessmentCo-Managed ITComprehensive IT SupportDesktop Monitoring and ManagementInfrastructure Support ServicesIT ConsultingIT Vendor ManagementManaged ServicesMicrosoft Hyper-VProfessional Server SupportRemote Monitoring & MaintenanceVMwareSoftware ServicesMicrosoft Office 365Microsoft Partner NetworkUnderstanding ITAutomationBusiness ContinuityBYODCloud ComputingGDPR ComplianceHIPAAIT Threat GlossaryNetwork SecurityPCI DSSRansomwareSOXThe Internet of ThingsThe Modern OfficeWindows 10NewsNews & Press ReleasesEvents CalendarOur NewsletterBlogContact UsSupportHow to Request SupportHelp Desk
You are here:
Home
/
About Us
/
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
JensenIT.com Privacy Policy
READ CAREFULLY. This Privacy Policy applies to use of the JensenIT.com website located at http://www.JensenIT.com (the "Site"). The Site is the property of JensenIT, Inc.
Our website allows you to buy products and services, apply for credit and receive newsletters, e-mails or other promotional information from us. We use the information that we collect about you to fulfill your product and service purchases and to create a more personalized online experience. This is just a brief overview, so please read on for more details about our Privacy Policy. This Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. Except as limited below, we reserve the right to use or disclose your personally identifiable information for business reasons in whatever manner desired.
Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you online. For some services, we either collect and transfer personal information to a service provider you have selected, or you may visit other merchants through links on our site who may collect and use your personal information. In those cases the third-party service provider or merchant's privacy policy will govern how your information is handled.
What information do we collect from you?
In order to better provide you with numerous products and services, JensenIT, Inc collects two types of information about its visitors: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site.
Personally Identifiable Information:
This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. Personal information is requested when you order a product or service. For example, this information might include your name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other payment information, and product details. With this information, JensenIT, Inc can fill your orders and better provide you with personalized services.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information:
This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you shop on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. For example, this information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet, browse and shop.
On an aggregated basis, we collect anonymous data related to the pages, products, downloads and other content that is sampled, clicked on, streamed, searched for, transferred from and downloaded. Except as otherwise limited in this Policy, we may disclose, sell, trade, or rent Non-Personally Identifiable Information to others without your consent.
Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide JensenIT, Inc’s visitors with a superior customized online experience. We use the customer contact information to fill orders, contact purchasers to inform them of their order status, to send promotional information, to enhance the operation of our site and administer our systems.
Demographic data also may be collected at our site from third party advertising servers, content servers, or web site analysis agents who provide us with the zip code and area code associated with a visitor's server, along with pages viewed on our site. We review the actions of the JensenIT, Inc visitors on an aggregate basis to determine customers' preferences. JensenIT, Inc also does research on our visitors' demographics, interests, and pages viewed based on the information provided to us during ordering, a promotion, from our server log files, from our web site analysis agents, or from contests, drawings or surveys. We will use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site use, to improve our product offerings, and to customize our site's content, layout, and services. We receive reports from third party ad servers, content servers, or web site analysis agents that tells us how many ads were presented and clicked upon or what content was served or viewed.
Ordering:
When you order from us, we collect personally identifiable information from you. If you order one of our products or services, we will collect and maintain your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, order number, referring URL, IP address, page you bought from and a password. We collect this, and other information, as disclosed in this Policy, in order to fill your order, to communicate with you about your order and to send you promotional materials. Before confirming your order, you will have the opportunity to review the product order form and make changes and additions to the information it contained and these changes will be automatically kept for future use. We may require additional verifications or information before accepting any order.
Newsletters, Promotional E-mails and Personalized On-line Ads:
We offer free newsletters, promotional e-mails and personalized on-line advertisements as a service to our customers. We will send you newsletters and e-mails periodically listing current specials and deals. You may "opt-out," or unsubscribe from our newsletters, emails or personalized on-line advertisements by following any unsubscribe instructions in any e-mail, newsletter or personalized on-line advertisement you receive from us. After doing so, if you have opted out of receiving all newsletters, all promotional emails or all personalized on-line ads, you will not receive future promotional emails, newsletters or personalized on-line advertisements (as applicable), unless you open a new account, enter a contest, or otherwise subsequently sign up to receive newsletters, emails or personalized on-line advertisements.
With whom do we share your information?
Fulfillment:
The information collected by JensenIT, Inc is used for processing orders, keeping you informed about your order status, for statistical purposes, for improving our site and its performance, to serve ads, and to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you.
Other Parties Generally:
We may provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third parties, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information.
Products Advertised on Our Site:
Where you order or sign up for goods or services offered through our site, but sold directly to you by a third party or fulfilled by a third party, we give your personal information to that third party to facilitate the sale of such goods or services (e.g., orders shipped from distribution or direct from the manufacturer).
What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?
In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order.
Within JensenIT, Inc, your information is kept on password protected, limited access servers. Wherever possible and applicable, JensenIT, Inc servers reside behind a corporate firewall that maintains controls on access to the system from both our internal network and the Internet.
Contacting JensenIT, Inc about privacy questions or concerns
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact JensenIT, Inc by sending a letter to:
Attn: Privacy Policy JensenIT, Inc 1689 Elk Blvd. Des Plaines, Illinois, 60016
Privacy Policy changes
This Privacy Policy was last changed on January 1, 2015. If JensenIT, Inc makes changes to any terms or conditions of the Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted in this document so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and to whom we will disclose it. We may change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we tell you otherwise.
Customer
Login
Your Email
Password
Remember me
Forgot your password?
Create an Account?
Latest
Blog
Tip of the Week: 5 Ways to Easily Identify a Phishing Attack
If you’ve been reading this blog for any length of time, you’ve seen us reference a phishing attack. Whether you are being asked by some supposed Nigerian prince to fork over money or you are getting an email by what seems to be your bank that directs you to download an attachment, you are probably a potential victim of a phishing scam. The difference between being a potential victim and a victim is knowing how to identify it. Today, we’ll give you five ways to identify a phishing message so that you—or your company—won’t be scammed.
Read More
Contact
Us
Learn more about what JensenIT can do for your business.
(847) 803-0044
JensenIT1689 Elk Blvd Des Plaines, Illinois 60016
Facebook URL of JensenIT Twitter URL of JensenIT LinkedIn URL of JensenIT RSS URL of JensenIT
Copyright
JensenIT. All Rights Reserved.
×
Sign up for our Newsletter!
Hey! Before you go, subscribe to our newsletter for IT tech tips and advice!
Please wait, we are processing the form !!
